What we need here is a magical typewriter.
What do you think?
Savana, what do you think?
I'm sorry, Liam,
but we're not doing a fantasy film.
Turn your back.
Borj, let's get Tristan in the room.
- Oh, come on...
- Deedee, please delete the video.
Why would I do that?
I'm going to sell this.
Love.
Joyce...
Joyce.
Savana's video while drunk dancing in a club
is now viral on social media.
Savana.
Hans.
I came back
as soon I saw the video sent by my friend.
How are you feeling?
Have you talked to Aunt Joanne already?
I will hear it from you now.
You were captured on video while drinking!
Can't you see or feel
that I need even just a little space, Mom?
If I had let you decide for yourself,
you would have probably
lost your career already.
Everyone, let's proceed
to the conference room.
I'm sorry
that our meeting coincided with the audition.
Let's go?
Here, this way.
Boss bro.
Congressman's new protégé is so cocky.
Looks like
the meeting will be more action-packed
than the auditions.
You and your big mouth.
You better help Megan
since Leroy and Deedee are
on emergency leave.
Where is it?
Over there? Should I follow them?
- Of course.
- Okay, Boss Bro.
Congressman Ramon's team has decided
to replace Tristan
because he only has a 50-50 chance
of winning the elections.
So, Josh will run for Congress.
And because we can't afford to lose,
the Congressman's PR team
raised a big concern
about our movie production.
He doesn't want
to get associated with Savana anymore.
You all know why we're making this movie
before the elections.
We don't want to give the voters,
especially the rivals,
a weapon to destroy our candidate.
Excuse me. Excuse me, Sir Vergil.
Let's get straight to the point.
Is this because of Savana's viral video?
We already issued a statement.
We also did an interview.
Didn't you watch it?
Here!
- Here it is!
- Mommy.
Savana...
Your video getting wild in a bar
is far from your image.
I'm sure Blacksmith isn't
the only one reacting to this scandal.
What does your TV network say?
The products that you endorse?
Do you think the damage control
you and your mother did was enough?
VLH...
In this industry,
we sometimes encounter problems
we cannot overcome.
Like what, VLH?
The bashing and cyberbullying of Savana?
Should we get affected by those things?
Shouldn't we focus on what matters more?
And that is to create a good movie
regardless of the issues thrown at us.
Issues that have
nothing to do with our project.
You don't know anything
about this industry, Liam.
Why don't you just go back to Casa Fuerte?
Weren't you the ones
who dumped me here in Blacksmith?
It's my right to protect this project.
That's enough.
I will let the Congressman decide.
This is not just about the movie.
This is also about Josh's bid for Congress.
Let's take a break.
I know how cutthroat showbiz is.
But... I still get surprised.
Your issues seem to be on schedule.
You have new issues every day.
Different issues.
I hope you're okay.
I'm used to it.
Actually, my past issues were worse.
I used to get affected by it. But now...
Are you and your mom okay?
I know how strong her personality is.
I mean... for sure,
you two can get through this.
Thank you for the pep talk.
It was great working with you, Mr. Herrera.
What?
I know the drill.
I'm sure I'm getting axed.
It's so easy to replace actors.
Joyce, if only I could take away your burden,
I would do it.
Mr. Herrera.
It was great working with you.
We'll proceed with Josh and Savana's film.
Savana will remain as
the film's leading lady.
Joanne...
this is the men's restroom.
I know, Congressman.
Oh, Congressman... about your other godson...
Is he sure about his identity?
Oh my God.
Look. He's dancing.
It's so funny.
Look.
- Look.
- Friend, look.
He's dancing his heart out.
Look.
- Look at that.
- Hey, what's that?
What's that? Let me see it.
- What's that?
- Nothing.
I said let me see. Give it to me.
Please send it to me. Hurry.
Send it to me.
- Sorry?
- Send it to me
if you don't want to lose your job
here in my resort.
Send it to me right now.
Okay.
I've already sent it.
Why are you getting him drunk? Look at him.
Okay, get back to work.
I'll let you and your daughter
win this round.
Excuse me.
Thank you, Liam.
Thank you for not giving up on this project.
Thank you for not letting
the issues against me affect you.
All's well that ends well, right?
I can now relax.
How about you?
I'm happy that we're still doing the project.
I just wonder why
the congressman didn't replace me.
Savana, are you coming home with me?
No, Mommy.
Hans and I still need to go somewhere.
Okay.
I'm done with work today, anyway.
I'll go ahead.
Joyce, after all the wrong things I've done,
all I can do now is stay by your side.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Miss Via.
I know we're swamped with work,
but I already found the woman
you wanted me to research about.
The woman named Joycelyn Trinidad.
You can leave for now, Nicole.
Okay.
So...
[Trinidad Joycelyn Cruz]
Actually, there are a lot of permutations.
There is Jocelyn, Joycely,
and Joyce Marie Trinidad.
But this is the only Joycelyn Trinidad
we found.
I had to convince my ex-boyfriend who's a cop
to give me that.
So, she's been a domestic helper in France
for 30 years now.
She's a bit old.
Probably that's why we can't find her
on the internet.
Probably, she's not too techie.
Is she the one you're looking for?
If you don't mind me asking, Miss...
who is she?
Is she a distant relative?
Or a former housemaid that you want to help?
Who is she?
No.
I don't think she's the one I'm looking for.
Sorry, Miss Via.
I probably missed something.
I'll keep looking.
Please.
Sir Liam, here's the fight director's
body of work.
He's actually trained by a Chinese director,
who is also an expert in martial arts movies.
So here it is.
Savana...
Are you coming home with me?
No, Mom.
Hans and I still need to go somewhere.
Sir Liam?
Yeah.
Well, if Phil and the rest of the team
already approved it,
we can already set a meeting with him.
Okay, Sir.
Can I see it?
Here.
Maybe we can use Savana's meltdown
for publicity
if we're not replacing her.
We can parallel it
to her character in the movie.
I think her character will have a fall
from grace, right?
It's perfect
for what she's going through right now.
- This one.
- Liam.
Can we talk?
Yes, Uncle.
Excuse me, Sir.
Sir.
How does it feel to encounter problems
early on with the production?
Are you talking about Savana, Uncle?
Well, she's a strong woman.
So I know
she won't let the issues affect her.
And about our film,
we hope the audience will still accept it
without bias against the actors.
Are you really serious about this?
What?
Of course, Uncle.
This is the chance my dad gave me
to prove myself.
I don't think you understand.
I let Danilo put you here in Blacksmith
to lie low.
People have their eyes on you at Casa Fuerte.
But we cannot totally lose you there.
Uncle, I thought
you and Dad entrusted me with this film?
Of course!
I want Josh to win a seat in congress
through this film.
But Vergil can do this.
I'm already invested in this project, Uncle.
This is also my dream.
I don't think you understand, Liam!
What the hell are you talking about, Liam?
You sound like a different person!
Get your act together!
I let you deal
with whatever mid-life crisis
you're going through!
But when I say
you will return to Casa Fuerte,
you will!
Do you understand?
I'll tell you something.
A part of me thinks
it's a blessing in disguise
if you lose your project in Blacksmith.
What made you think that?
You know me.
When you said
your movie is a little physically demanding,
I couldn't help but worry.
Hans, this is my dream project.
I'm so tired of doing unchallenging roles.
I always portray a damsel in distress
who needs to be saved by the hero.
I don't want anything like that anymore.
And besides, I'm happy with Blacksmith.
Because in Blacksmith...
they listen to my opinion,
my suggestions, ideas... everything.
Blacksmith knows how to make action films.
It's not a big deal, actually.
But if Liam can assure your safety,
I won't have a problem with it.
I'm just worried.
Hi, Savana. Can I have a picture with you?
Is it okay?
- I'll do it. I'll take your picture.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Thank you.
Okay. One, two...
- Okay.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Hey. Isn't that Savana?
Have you seen her video?
She was so drunk.
She was out of control.
Yes. She said nasty things about her mother.
I used to like her so much.
I even wished to have a daughter like her.
But now, I know what kind of daughter
she really is.
Ungrateful.
Right.
I will probably disown her
if she's my daughter.
Sorry...
Do you want to go somewhere else?
Sir!
Bill out, please.
We're going to bill out.
- I'm going to get your bill.
- No need.
It's okay. Here's the money.
Sir, this is too much.
It's okay. You can have the rest, okay?
I'm sorry we're in a hurry. Thank you.
Where are we going?
Just follow me, come on.
She walked out.
I know the head chef here.
I'm sure you'll enjoy the food.
Where's the chef? Chef!
Hans.
How are you, bro?
- Chef JR! Nice to see you.
- How are you?
- Nice to see you. I'm good.
- How's life?
Thank you, looks like you already
have food prepared for us.
No problem.
- We don't have privacy at the other cafe.
- I understand.
By the way, do I still have to introduce her?
Of course, I know you.
- Hi.
- Savana.
- Hello.
- My name's JR.
Please, have a seat.
Savana.
We serve nothing but the best.
I will let you try my specialty.
Looks like it will be a cheat day.
Ladies first.
Here you go, Ma'am.
- Bro.
- Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
- I'll come back later.
- Thank you.
Remember, you're on a diet.
- Be careful.
- Hans, please. Just today.
Go ahead.
Round two?
So you heard it right from Uncle Ramon.
He and Dad agreed to let me babysit you.
And now you're imposing yourself here.
All our lives,
you're the best in everyone's eyes.
Why does Uncle Ramon talk
like he has more authority than dad?
What the...
Have you already forgotten?
We don't talk about things like that!
Oh, Liam!
You really have gone insane!
Fine. Even though I don't like you,
I will let it slide just this once.
I will pretend you forgot
that Uncle Ramon owns us.
What do you mean he owns us?
Go on. Make it louder!
Blacksmith Productions, Casa Fuerte,
and our other businesses are his.
We're lucky Congressman Ramon
lets us take care of his businesses.
He'll bring us with him to the top.
So, you can go against everyone
except Congressman Ramon.
If you do that, you'll get what you deserve.
What you did in Casa Fuerte...
you're lucky
because his daughter is your girlfriend.
If not, he would have buried you alive.
Get out of here.
I don't want to get in trouble
because of you.
Leave!
There.
How are you, guys?
Just a little something for you.
- Bring it home with you.
- Chef, thank you.
I'll bring it home.
Her mother might scold her
if she sees her eating this.
Chef, your food is so good.
Thank you so much.
My pleasure, my pleasure.
I will expect you guys to come back, okay?
Yes, Chef.
Looks like I'm going to be
your regular customer.
I'll look forward to it.
Okay.
Bro, nice to see you. Thank you again.
I hope she's already your girlfriend
the next time you visit.
I hope so, too.
Let's go?
Thank you.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
Let's go.
Hans...
Can you give me time alone?
I'll just book a ride home.
There's somewhere I need to drop by first.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
Don't worry about me.
Okay.
Be safe, okay?
Okay, see you.
I had fun. Thank you.
Thanks to you, too.
Okay, bye.
I'll get going.
Okay. Be safe, okay?
Hi, Mom.
Son.
Wow, where are we going?
Looks like we're going on a vacation.
Just me.
Why are you not bringing me with you?
If I can do that, why not?
I'm already used to traveling alone
on my birthday.
Is it because
I was busy with work in Casa Fuerte?
Son, I'm not forcing you to come with me.
I've long accepted that you're always busy.
We owe Casa Fuerte a lot.
You wouldn't be able to pay for my operation
if it wasn't for your job, right?
So it's okay with you that
I'm not there on special occasions
like your birthday?
Who knows?
Since you're no longer in Casa Fuerte,
you might be able to come with me again
on my birthday. Right?
Ouch.
Mom, are you okay?
Son, won't the doctor get mad
that you brought me out?
Mom...
I want you to be happy.
Happy birthday, Mom.
Thank you, son.
But you don't have to do this.
Mom...
You know I can't do that.
This day is special.
Because it's your birthday.
Special...
Because it may be
my last birthday celebration.
Come on, Mom.
I don't want you saying things like that.
Mom...
Mom, you'll get better.
And you'll still celebrate
many birthdays with me,
my wife, and my son.
Okay?
I love you.
One, two, three, go.
- Happy birthday, Mama Tess!
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday, Grandma.
Happy birthday, Grandma.
Give Grandma a kiss.
Mama Tess, happy birthday.
You got that, Hon?
- There you go.
- Of course.
- Mama Tess, make a wish.
- Make a wish first.
One, two, three...
- Yay!
Happy birthday, Mom.
Happy birthday, Grandma.
Thank you for the overflowing love.
We love you so much.
- I love you, Mom.
- I love you, Mama Tess.
- Happy birthday, Grandma.
- Thank you.
- My grandson.
- Happy birthday.
We love you.
Dance for grandma.
Dance, come on.
- Come here, dear.
- Show grandma your dance.
- Ready, set, go!
- Show her.
Happy birthday, happy birthday,
happy birthday, Grandma!
Happy birthday, Grandma.
Yes, son.
I just had a mild headache.
Maybe I've been on the gadget for too long.
I told you. You should get some rest, Mom.
You better go to your room.
Get some rest for now.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Hello, Mom?
Sorry, I can't talk right now.
Savana, where are you?
Why am I hearing crickets?
I'm at a spa right now.
It's the ambient sound.
I'll call you back. Bye.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Dad...
Let's go home.
Sorry, dear, if I followed you.
It's because I miss you.
Are you sure no one saw you come here?
No one.
Dad...
I should be the one to apologize.
This has become our normal setup.
You have to sneak just to see me.
I saw it somewhere.
Joyce.
A father should protect his child.
Maybe this is the sacrifice we have to make.
If only I was a father
you could introduce to people...
Someone you can be proud of...
Then, you won't have a hard time.
But I'm the one who brought us
into this situation.
Dad, no.
Always remember that it's not your fault
that I am having a hard time.
I'm having a hard time
because I'm always pretending.
I'm tired of this, Dad.
This perfect image called Savana...
Dad, I don't want any of it anymore.
I'm tired of the image
that Mom has created for me.
It's like a point of no return.
I promise, Mom.
From now on, a lot will change.
I'm starting to realize my shortcomings
in this new life I have.
I will prioritize what's important.
But I will make sure I'm no longer
indebted to Casa Fuerte before I resign.
Good night, Mom.
Do you think I won't find out
where you've been?
I'm tracking you on my phone.
I saw where you went.
You went to see your father.
Mommy...
In this industry,
a single pest can ruin your name!
Why do you treat Dad like that?
Why?
How do you want me to treat your father?
Like he's the head of the family?
Stop seeing your father!
It's enough that we're feeding him...
and financially supporting him!
I already have a lot on my plate
because of you.
And you keep doing this!
Sir, my artist is asking
when you will take her pictures.
We came here first.
Later.
The network has given me
a list for the catalog shoot.
So as of now,
Savana isn't the priority, okay?
Thank you.
What did he say?
Just a couple more artists
and you'll go next.
Just be more patient.
Hi, Sir Pao.
Hi, Maxine!
You look good.
You're getting prettier by the day.
Well, congrats.
I heard you are being considered
to be the lead star
of the new prime time show.
Do your best.
This will be your big break.
Yes, Sir Pao.
You know how showbiz works. It's so volatile.
So...
you really should take care of your career.
Especially in the time of social media, gosh.
One serious issue can cause your downfall.
So...
You may be... in the artist catalog today...
But the next day, you can be out.
Right?
Let's eat first.
Yeah. We should.
I thought there was food...
But it's actually someone else's life
they were feasting on.
Happy fiesta!
Sis, you can now pass through.
[Records Section]
Hi, Ma'am.
Can I have a copy
of my mother's medical records?
Only the patient can request it.
Or if she gave a consent letter.
Ma'am, my mother is in...
Liam! What are you doing here?
Are you here for a consultation?
How's Ma'am Tess?
Does she feel anything unusual again?
She's okay, Doc. My mom's doing fine.
I'm here to check her medical records.
What for?
Nothing serious.
I'm just organizing our records.
But I was told that I couldn't get it.
Don't worry.
I'll request your mother's records for you.
Thank you so much, Doc.
Thank you.
Okay. Bye.
Sis, have some juice first.
I'll just use the restroom.
Thank you, sis.
Girls, did you see Savana's face earlier?
She looks like a poor cat.
Everyone's avoiding her.
At least we're not the only ones
who don't want to get associated with her.
Don't tell anyone,
but I heard her show can be cut short.
I won't be surprised.
She's now a liability to all the shows.
Well, now it's your time to shine, Maxine.
I doubt.
You know, in this industry,
your fans can get too affected
by your personal affairs.
But they'll also care
if their idols are good or bad people.
So, what are you saying?
Are you saying I won't get famous
because I have an attitude problem?
I didn't say that.
You said it yourself.
Is that yours?
Avoid sweets.
You might not fit
in the gown I brought with me.
Let's go, girls.
Savana, hasn't the photographer
called you yet?
Savana.
You were there the whole time?
So you heard everything?
Everything.
Thank you...
for defending me.
I wanted to fight back, but...
What for?
Let me have it.
I enjoyed getting cheeky with them.
Via, what brings you here?
My magazine's publishing house
will produce your network's catalog.
So, the owner asked me to
oversee the photo shoot.
Queenie, are those the outfits
of Maxine and her friends?
Yes, Miss Via.
Let me choose it for them.
Okay.
Here are my initial choices.
Here, here.
You think is it okay?
They're okay.
I just have a few things in mind.
- Okay.
- I might change it.
Okay.
I hate it. I'm getting itchy.
Maxine and her friends' dresses
are so last season.
Excuse me.
Miss Via of Escale Magazine is their stylist.
Sorry, Miss Via.
I'll let you know once the magazine publishes
your shoot and interview, Savana.
Do we have a problem, Via?
I want all of you to know me as Joyce.
Is it just a coincidence,
or is it Savana the Joycelyn Trinidad
you're asking me to find?
You tell me.
Is there something I have to worry about?
Have you watched
the latest video about Savana?
I'm watching it now, Borj.
Who in the right mind would do such a thing?
Savana, what did you do?
What did you do?
Who did you tell your real name to?
Can we talk?
I thought we were friends.
What did you do?
Dex?
Dex.